我要你宣布  罗杰  我们好派他们去
I want a Declaration, Roger. So we can send them in.
但总统女士
But, Madam President--
国民警卫队  联邦紧急事务管理署和环保署
I have the Guard, FEMA and the EPA
都调动好了  就在城外等着
mobilized and waiting on the outskirts of that town.
我刚跟精炼厂联系过
I just got off the phone with the refinery.
泄露已经要烧尽了
The leak is well on its way to burning off.
据我所知  空气质量达到了危险程度
My understanding is that the air quality is dangerous.
污染的确加重了  是的
The levels are somewhat elevated, yes,
-但风向对我们有利  -但也可能变化
- but the winds are in our favor. - And subject to change.
风就是如此
That's how wind works.
一两天内一切都会结束
This will all be over in a day or two,
但要让民众撤离家园...
the idea of keeping these families out of their homes--
这谨慎的预防措施
This is a prudent precaution
我坐镇时  就希望采取这种措施
and on my watch, that's what I want to happen.
我觉得不应该夸大情况
I don't think we should exaggerate the situation.
你还记得选举当晚你的情况吗  州长
Do you remember where you were on election night, Governor?
我可记得
Because I do.
你本来要输了
You were going to lose.
统计学上讲  你是根本不该赢的
Statistically, there is no reason you should have won.
你考虑的时候
Keep the phone away from your mouth
别把电话靠在嘴边  州长
while you're thinking, Governor.
我听得到你的喘气声
I can hear you breathing.
是
Yes.
我觉得我是有必要宣布进入紧急状态
I do believe I need to declare a state of emergency.
当然了  这是你的决定
Of course, it's your call.
我向你保证
And I assure you,
联邦政府会全力支持你
you will have the full support of the federal government.
我曾对自己保证不会像他那样
I promised myself I wouldn't be like him.
但那就是弗兰西斯的典型做法  是吧
That was textbook Francis, wasn't it?
但他像递盐罐一样把我交给了他们
But he handed me over to them like a shaker of salt
现在  他们不肯放手了
and now they won't let go.
这是他们自作自受
This is a wound of their own making.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President?
请进
Yeah, come in.
需要我等您一会儿吗  先生
Do you need a moment, sir?
不用
No, no.
怎么了
What is it?
好
Okay.
州长
Governor?
翻译   草草
时间轴   想念Gallifrey的wholock
后期   饿得慌
校对  草草
顾问  老杜
总监  草草
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
纸牌屋
第六季  第二集
他们说没事的
They said it was fine.
就是一股烂鸡蛋和垃圾的味儿
It smelled like rotten eggs and trash. That's all.
水龙头里都是这个味儿
You could smell it coming out of the faucet.
然后我儿子  他开始流鼻血了  我就想
And then my son, his-- his nose started to bleed and I thought,
-"跟这有关吗"  -你儿子现在在哪呢
- "Is that related?" - Where is your little boy right now?
现在吗  他跟他妈在做验伤
Now? He's in triage with his mom.
-那小家伙是我的心肝  -我知道
- He's my heart, that little guy. - No, I know. I know.
但女士  我可以问问吗
But, ma'am. If I may. You--
您得告诉我们  这是不是真的
You have to tell us. Is this real or not?
因为  起初他们说我们不需要撤离
Because at first they said that we don't need to evacuate,
但突然又改口说得撤离
and then all of a sudden that we should.
我要告诉你  一切都会没事的
I want you to know everything is going to be all right.
我保证
I promise you.
我们指望着那工厂通知我们情况呢
We were relying on that plant to keep us informed.
先生  你和你的安全
Sir, you and your safety
才是最重要的
is the most important thing.
事实上  贝尔波特所有的家庭
In fact, all of the families of Bellport,
才是唯一重要的
nothing else matters.
我要感谢奥姆斯泰德州长
I want to give my thanks to Governor Olmstead
他今早快速果决地
for his quick and decisive act this morning
宣布了进入紧急状态
in declaring a state of emergency.
联邦紧急事务管理署  环保署
We have FEMA, we have EPA,
俄亥俄州国民警卫队
the Ohio National Guard.
都来了
They're all here.
没有人应该感到不安全
No one should ever feel unsafe.
...在她自己家里
In her own home.
你怎么会完全不知道呢  马克
And how is it you have no idea, Mark?
-这无所谓  -这很有所谓
- It doesn't matter. - Oh, it does matter.
这说明了我们的关系多靠不住
It speaks to this untenable arrangement.
我说了待会儿再说那个  先考虑回应
Later, I said. Let's stay focused on our response.
她今早本都已经要签署法案了
She was all set to sign the bill this morning.
我们叫了摄像师和记者什么的候着
We had photographers, a press pool waiting, the whole thing.
-但她没签  是吧  -我这就过去
- But she didn't sign it, did she? - I'm on my way there now.
因为她在忙着
Because she was too busy
无中生有地制造紧急状况
manufacturing an emergency out of nothing.
别忘了是谁升级了事态  好吗
Look, let's not forget who escalated this. Okay?
什么
Excuse me?
如果我们要合作  比尔
If we're working together, Bill,
我需要参与每一个决定
I need to be included in every decision.
每一个
Every one.
我们没什么好谈的了
This conversation's over.
老天爷啊
Oh, for God's sakes.
我会去贝尔波特跟安奈特碰头
I'll join Annette in Bellport.
不  你别去
No, you won't.
你们中有一人到场就够糟了
One of you showing up on site is bad enough.
安奈特  给我打电话
Annette, call me back.
马克
Mark.
马克  你还在吗
Mark, are you still there?
是的
Yes.
让我跟他谈谈  我再打给你
Let me talk to him. I'll circle back.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我是凯尔茜·斯图尔特
My name is Kelsey Stewart.
代理新闻发言人
I'm the deputy press secretary,
今天我将为大家回答问题
and I will be taking your questions today.
莎拉
Sarah.
奥姆斯泰德州长是否真的
Is it true that Governor Olmstead
对宣布进入紧急状态很抗拒
was resistant to declaring a state of emergency?
州长的确宣布了进入紧急状态
The Governor did declare a state of emergency,
白宫也赞同了
and the White House concurs.
工厂出了很大的问题
Something very wrong happened in that plant.
请说
Yes.
阿卡斯公司在泄露和爆炸事件方面
Arcas has been slow to provide any details
迟迟不肯公布细节
when it comes to the leak and explosion.
更不用说两人在事故中丧生了
Not to mention the two lives lost in the accident.
他们跟白宫配合了吗
Have they been cooperating with the White House?
现在总统去了第一线
Now that the president is on the ground,
他们似乎是更加愿意配合了
it seems that, yes, they have been more agreeable.
但这不是该问的问题
That's not the real question, though.
该有人问问
Somebody might want to ask,
谢泼德无限责任公司怎么不出来说话
where is Shepherd Unlimited in all of this?
阿卡斯精炼厂是该家族集团的子公司
The Arcas Refinery is a subsidiary of the family's conglomerate.
你是说谢泼德家族
Are you saying that the Shepherds
清楚工厂的问题吗
are personally aware of problems at the plant?
谁该负责  负怎样的责任
Who is responsible and how
这正是白宫和总统
is all the White House and the president
此刻想要查清的问题
are trying to find out at this point.
这会对总统
Will this have any effect
准备签署的去监管法案有影响吗
on the regulatory bill on the president's desk?
总统不久后就会就此发表讲话
The president will be speaking on that shortly.
马可斯
Marcus.
总统在前总统死前
Was the president planning to divorce the former president
有打算与他离婚吗
in the days leading up to his death?
我们...
Let's...
-副总统先生  -大家早上好
- Mr. Vice President. - Morning, everyone.
希望斯图尔特小姐不会介意我回答几个问题
I hope Miss Stewart won't mind me taking a couple of questions.
副总统先生  请回答一个问题
Mr. Vice President, one question!
马可斯  你的消息源是谁
Marcus, who's your source?
-匿名官员  -不  这行不通了
- Unnamed officials. - Nope. We don't do that anymore.
我们要名字  你能说吗
We need names. You have a name?
说真的  你是哪听来的
I mean really, where do you get this?
前总统
The former president
生前的最后一晚
spent his last night alive
是在白宫他妻子身边度过的  就是这样
next to his wife in the White House. Period.
至于贝尔波特
As for Bellport...
知道全部事实之前  不要急着下结论
let's not jump to conclusions before all the facts are in.
还有什么
What else?
我们还在逐户查看  但这只是为防万一
We still going door to door, but it's really a precaution.
床位够吗
Are there enough beds?
我们有几间教堂地下室
We have a few church basements
如果有必要  还有当地监狱
and the local jail if we need more.
反正空气里还剩下的硫化氢
Whatever hydrogen sulfide there is left in the air
也要消散了
is already dissipating.
再过一两天  大家就能回自己的床上睡觉
In a day or two, people will be back sleeping in their own beds.
您得明白
You have to understand,
总统女士
Madam President,
几乎所有人都会对化学品过度反应
most everyone overreacts when it comes to chemicals.
我们有多年的经验
We have years of experience--
那死于事故的人呢
And the men who died in the accident?
那的确很悲惨  他们都是好员工
That's tragic, of course. They were valued employees.
都是社区里的成员  他们不可替代
Members of the community. There's no way to replace them.
比尔·谢泼德呢
And Bill Shepherd?
-怎么  -他来过电话吗
- Yes. - Have you heard from him?
我把情况通知了他和其他合伙人
I've kept him informed, as well as all of our partners.
比尔直接给我打过电话
Bill called me directly.
他们准备采取一切必要措施
They're ready to do whatever's needed.
他们对贝尔波特非常重要
They're important to Bellport.
他们建了当地的运动场
They built the local stadium.
还有这个体育馆  他们出资...
Even this gymnasium. They contributed--
我很清楚他们家族的慈善事业
No, I'm well aware of the family's philanthropy.
我问的不是那个
That wasn't the question.
是的  谢泼德先生一直在密切关注局势
Yes, Mr. Shepherd has been monitoring the situation closely.
我想在这一代巡视一圈
I would like to tour the area.
可以吗  州长
Is that a problem, Governor?
当然  据我所知没问题
No, no, not to my understanding.
我还想带您去
I was hoping to get you over to--
我们的验伤处
to where we set up our triage.
我们最好还是按日程来...
It might be best if we stick to the itinerary--
我想自己亲眼看看
I'd actually like to see it for myself.
当然  除非你们说不行
Unless, of course, you tell me otherwise.
不  当然可以
No, of course not.
警卫队标记了已撤离的房子
The guard marks the doors of the evacuees.
都是标准程序
Pretty standard procedure.
停车  我好像看到了人
Stop the car. I think I see someone.
停车
Stop the car.
总统女士  我们会叫人再回来的
Madam President, we'll have someone circle back.
马上停车
Stop the car now.
该死
Damn it.
她安全吗
Is she safe?
没有百分之百的安全
Nothing is 100% safe.
有人吗  有人在吗
Hello. Anyone here?
那男孩差点瞎掉一只眼睛
The boy could have lost an eye.
我们不能那么对待别人
That's not how we treat people.
她怎么能这么做
How could she?
天呐  伊丽莎白  行了
My God, Elizabeth, stop it.
我养的是个女儿还是野兽
Am I raising a daughter or an animal?
他们才是野兽  他们那么攻击她
They're the animals, the way they attacked her.
好啊  替她说话吧你就
Oh, of course, take her side. Of course!
她也该了解这世界了
It's time she learned about the world.
漂亮姑娘要对她们的美貌负责
Pretty girls have a responsibility to their beauty.
肯定是她激了那些男孩
I'll bet she dared those boys.
真丢脸
Shame on her.
你怎么就不能乖乖听话
Why can't you just do as you're told?
是啊  为什么
Why, indeed?
总统女士  总统女士
Madam President! Madam President.
总统女士
Madam President...
我们最好回去了
might be best if we head back.
房子安全吗
So, the house is safe?
那喝一口
Drink it then.
我猜也是
I thought so.
谢泼德自由基金会
-但我在答应什么  -我可以给你读一遍
- But what am I agreeing to? - I can read it for you.
我识字
I can read.
这是干什么的
And what's this for?
这是让应用能分析出
That lets the app figure out
我们怎样才能最好地施以帮助
how we can be most helpful.
可以根据你的具体需求来制定计划
It can be tailored to your specific needs.
我们想让你及时了解情况
We want to keep you informed.
我们希望你在事发前就知道要发生什么
We want you to know what happens before it happens.
这是不能靠政府的
You can't trust the government to do that.
你好  我是赛斯·格雷森
Hello, my name is Seth Grayson.
认识你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
我是谢泼德自由基金会的
I'm with Shepherd Freedom Foundation,
可以跟你谈谈吗
can I talk to you for a second?
当然  我看了宣传册
Sure thing. I was looking at the pamphlet saying just...
同意
是总统
It's the president.
总统女士
Madam President.
是谁的主意  把戒指放他床上
Whose idea was it? To leave it on his bed?
别在这儿说
Not here.
谢泼德自由基金会是来帮忙的
The Shepherd Freedom Foundation is here to help.
联邦政府将帮助你们
The federal government is here to help you.
是啊  总统女士
Yes, Madam President.
美国的问题要得到解决
The only way America's problems will be solved
就得靠政府和私企联手
is through alliances between government and private industry,
各司其职
each doing its part.
我跟三军统帅可是老交情了
The Commander in Chief and I go way back.
是啊  我知道谢泼德家族会
We do. And I know I have the full cooperation
完全配合我的工作
from the Shepherd family.
阿卡斯这种公司
The blatant disregard for human life
对生命的公然漠视...
exhibited by companies like Arcas--
阿卡斯公司是一心想保护其员工的安全的
Arcas is committed to the safety of its workers.
如果能得到助力
And with the help of...
比如正确的立法  像是《未来法案》
the right kind of legislation, like the FUTURE Act.
此刻正在接受审核
Which is under review at the moment.
法案通过前
Until then,
我要让环保署的犯罪调查处
I am hereby moving the EPA's Criminal Investigative Division
总统亲临化学泄露事故现场
进驻五角大楼
into the Pentagon,
他们将拥有军队的力量和资源支持
where it will enjoy the forces and the resources of our military.
他们会调查这起灾难的
And they will investigate this disaster.
我以我丈夫的坟墓起誓
I swear on my husband's grave,
我一定会查明究竟发生了什么
I will find out what happened here.
谢谢您的支持
Thank you for your support.
我本想放在你床上呢
I wanted to leave it on your bed.
别犯傻  那对我没用
Don't be thick, thick I can't use.
她真提出离婚了吗
Did she actually ask for a divorce?
那要紧吗
As if that matters.
如果我被要求给出这么问的凭据呢
And if I'm asked to justify the question?
他们不正面回答  就是足够的凭据了
It was justified the moment they didn't have an answer.
总统最不希望
The last thing the president wants
谈前总统的事了
is to be talking about the former president.
那我问问你
Let me ask you this.
总统甩开
How did your mother feel
你妈妈的手时  她是什么感觉
when the president yanked her hand away like that?
那不关你的事  马可斯
That's none of your goddamn business, Marcus.
总统抽手了吗
安德伍德尴尬握手时刻在网上疯传
-抽手  你是这么说的吗  -是啊
- Recoil? Is that the word you used? - Yeah,
我看就是这样
that's what I see.
-开玩笑吗  -不是
- Are you kidding me? - No.
我们真要浪费时间
Are we really gonna waste time
剖析两个女人之间的一个手势吗
dissecting a gesture between two women?
诺拉说得对  我当时在场
Nora's right. I was there.
没有什么抽手
There wasn't a recoil.
我同意汤姆的话
I gotta agree with Tom here.
我觉得安奈特·谢泼德是想硬拉着总统
For me, it's Annette Shepherd sort of manhandling the president
摆出胜利姿态  然后我看到她惊了一下
as a sign of victory, and then I detect a flinch.
就那么一下下  然后就抽了手
A slight flinch, then recoil.
-抽手...  -她是想切断自己
- Recoil? I mean-- - She's trying to separate herself
跟原本计划的弗兰西斯·安德伍德基金会
from the primary source of the funding for what was to be
-主资金源的关系  -这是关于过失
- the Francis J. Underwood Foundation. - This is about culpability.
她是去贝尔波特要求责任方负责的
She went to Bellport to hold those responsible accountable.
谢泼德无限责任公司这样的公司一直在被拖后腿
Companies like Shepherd Unlimited have been hamstrung.
所以她要签署的法案才如此重要
And that's why this bill on her desk is so important.
如果不能执行  立法就毫无意义
Legislation means nothing without proper enforcement.
给环保署武器只是固执
Weaponizing the EPA is wrongheaded.
而且根本不能...
And it does nothing to make--
与其给她的每一个行为找负面动机
Instead of ascribing negative motives to her every action,
我们为什么不能承认  安德伍德总统
why can't we just accept that President Underwood
去做了总统该做的事
was out there being presidential?
她让你
She put the fear of God
和你的新朋友感到害怕了  格雷森先生
into you and your new friends, Mr. Grayson.
做总统该做的事  就该签署法案
Being "Presidential" means signing the bill
更新陈旧的监管
and modernizing antiquated regulations.
你怎么会知道
As if you would know.
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
她丈夫  你曾是他政府的成员
Her husband, whose administration you were a part of,
本来就要...
was about to--
正准备建立一个慈善基金会
Was in the midst of setting up a philanthropic foundation.
她丈夫都要被起诉了
Her husband was about to be indicted.
什么  八字没一撇的事
Excuse me, there wasn't even a grand jury.
我有可靠消息称
I have it on good authority
他要被起诉了  而她要赦免他
he was about to be indicted, and she was about to pardon him.
但她还想离婚
But she also wanted a divorce.
好挽救自己  撇清关系
To save herself. Distance herself.
因为  拜托  难道你能说
Because, come on. Are you telling me
她对他的作为一无所知吗
she knew nothing of what he was up to?
-如果他有罪  她也有  -汤姆
- If he was guilty, she was guilty. - Tom? Tom,
我十分尊敬你
I have great respect for you
还有你在《先驱报》的工作
and the work you've done at the Herald.
但你能就她自己的表现来评述她吗
But are you even capable of defining her on her own terms?
抱歉  前一秒她还是悲伤寡妇
I'm sorry. One minute she's playing the grieving widow
-下一秒  她又借题发挥  -正是
- and the next, she's riding on the coattails. - Case in point.
虽然这么说很过分
This may be an unseemly thing to say,
但很可能
but it's quite possible
她丈夫的死  是总统走了大运
her husband's death was the president's lucky day.
你在这里可以畅所欲言
You can say whatever you want in here.
不管你有什么感觉  有什么想法
Whatever your feeling, thinking.
我质疑你的能力
I'm questioning your ability.
我的能力
My ability?
能不能分辨有道理的多疑和...
To tell the difference between justifiable paranoia and--
你还用那个词吗
Do you use the word anymore?
"疯狂"
"Madness?"
你对什么感到多疑
What do you feel paranoid about?
我自己吧
Myself, maybe.
我们为什么做我们做的事  为谁而做
Why we do what we do and for who?
谁更邪恶  医生
Who's more evil, Doctor,
发令者还是执行者
the taskmaster or the tasked?
你觉得弗兰西斯·安德伍德背叛了你吗
Do you feel like Francis Underwood betrayed you?
我觉得我在想是谁背叛了他
I guess I'm wondering who betrayed him.
你觉得呢
Who do you think?
你吗
You?
我不知道我们的治疗是否还能帮我
I don't know if these sessions are helping me anymore.
你为什么给我开药  医生
Why are you trying to drug me up, Doctor?
我觉得你该考虑一下
I think you should consider it.
氯氮平
Clozapine.
你肯定知道那会把人变成什么样
You must know what that does to a person.
现在又有了新的抗精神病药物  道格
They're a newer class of antipsychotics, Doug.
副作用
The side effects
不像以前的那些那么严重了
are not as sensational as some of the older ones.
你不非得这样受罪的
You don't have to suffer like this.
据我所知
From my understanding,
光是副作用就能让你显得
the side effects themselves can make you look--
我又得问  你是否还用"疯狂"这个词
And again, I'm asking you if you use this word "mad."
你开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
什么
Pardon?
你要一边看表
You're gonna talk to me about side effects
一边跟我聊副作用吗
while you look at your fucking clock?
不  你说得对  抱歉
No, you're right. I'm sorry.
我们还是明天下午继续吧
We're gonna have to take this up tomorrow afternoon.
这个话题要重大得多
This is a much bigger conversation.
不  我就现在说
No, I'm talking now.
抱歉  但你的时间到了
I'm sorry, but your time is up.
我才不在乎时间
I don't give a fuck about the time.
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper.
我很高兴你终于决定
I'm glad that you finally decided
好好利用你在这里的时间
to take advantage of your time here,
但你清楚规矩
but you know the rules.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
斯坦普先生  拜托
Mr. Stamper, please.
我也不想叫人来  但我会的
I don't want to have to call someone, but I will.
这太扯了
This is bullshit.
你舅舅可不高兴
Your uncle is not happy.
你知道你有多少次
Are you aware of how many of your sentences
张口就说他怎样吗
start with you quoting him?
他是对的
He's right.
这场闹剧适得其反
This circus backfired.
-我觉得你很棒  -你舅舅觉得
- I thought you were wonderful. - Your uncle thinks
-我们恶化了本就糟糕的局面  -妈妈
- we've made a bad situation worse. - Mom.
现在我成了这事的脸面人物了
Now I'm the face of this thing.
我们会利用这点帮我们的
Which we will use to our advantage.
她直接点了我们的名字
She called us out by name.
我们想怎么扭转舆论都行
We can spin it any way we want.
在国会想办法
Work the Congress.
就算她否决了法案  他们也能推翻她的决策
Even if she vetoes the bill, they can override it.
她反应过度了
She overreacted.
-还让我出了丑  -相信我
- And it made a fool of me. - I'm telling you,
你赢了
you won.
她觉得是她赢了
She thinks she did.
我认得那个表情  相信我
I know that expression, trust me.
她都想不好自己是麦克白夫人还是麦克白
She can't decide if she's Lady Macbeth or Macbeth.
-接下来让你舅舅处理  -不
- Your uncle takes it from here. - No.
这对我没什么私人感情
This isn't personal for me,
不像对你和比尔舅舅
not like it is for you and Uncle Bill.
你知道他讨厌关注
You know he hates the spotlight,
不管是对我们谁
for any of us.
他更喜欢老式的手腕
Prefers an old school way of dealing with things.
-我  -别以为你什么都知道了
- I... - And don't think you know everything.
因为不是的
Because you don't.
让我跟比尔舅舅谈谈
Let me talk to Uncle Bill.
他住进了海亚当斯酒店
He's taken a suite at the Hay-Adams.
弗兰克以前的房间
Frank's old room.
我是道格·斯坦普  联邦检察官女士
It's Doug Stamper, Madam US Attorney.
-你怎么拿到这个号码的  -别挂
- How did you get this number? - Don't hang up.
你再打来  让你的律师打去我办公室
The next call I expect is from your lawyer. In my office.
那可不好
You really shouldn't.
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper,
-这非常...  -我要撤供
- this is highly-- - I'm going to recant.
你在听吗
Are you there?
是的
Yes.
我要说明事情会怎么发展
I'm going to lay out how it's going to go.
如果我说错了  你就打断我
And you stop me at any point if I'm wrong.
但我要撤供
But I'm going to recant.
所以你需要换新的检察官
Which means you're going to need a new prosecutor.
因为你得回避
Because you're going to have to recuse yourself
好出庭指证我
so you can testify against me.
我们的这通电话
And this call we're on,
对你会不利的
is not going to look very good for you.
你在法庭上说的一切都会被判为传闻
Anything you say in court will be ruled hearsay.
法官
And the judge,
如果心情好会要求出示更多证据
if he's in a good mood, is going to ask for more evidence,
而你和你的新检察官却拿不出
and you and your new prosecutor aren't going to have any.
等等  等等
Et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
这个案子将无法成就你的事业
This case isn't going to make your career.
能改变你人生的案子
The case that's going change your life
是对克莱尔·安德伍德的起诉
is the prosecution of Claire Underwood.
真是可怕
It's gruesome,
这里发生的事
what's gone on here.
我亲自检查了所有登记簿
I checked all the log books myself.
还询问过行政管家
I spoke with the executive housekeeper.
她询问了员工  没人知道怎么回事
She interviewed the staff. Nobody knows anything.
那他的戒指是神奇地出现在了他的床上
So his ring just appeared on his bed by magic?
我感觉
My feeling is,
我们该关注的不是这件事本身
it's not the fact of it that we should be focusing on.
而是
But...
它意味着什么
what it means.
告诉我  马克  什么样的人会掘开他的坟墓
Tell me, Mark. What kind of people dig up a man's grave
把戒指从他冰冷僵硬的手指上
and remove a ring from his cold...
摘下来
hard finger?
就是那些在拿弗兰西斯的赦免
The same people that are generating this drum beat
和你的离婚请求做文章的人
about Francis' pardon and your divorce.
是你在刺激他们
You are daring them.
是你把事情闹大了  现在他们不肯罢休了
You've turned it into a spectacle, and now they will not stop.
相信我  这些人不会罢休的
Believe me. These people will not rest.
你得做出弥补
You need to make amends.
为对她的轻慢吗
For slighting her?
-为指出他们吗  -你得给他们点什么
- For identifying them? - You have to give them something.
-我不相信这份法案  -该死的
- I don't believe in the bill. - Oh, goddamn it!
这份法案  你在听吗
This bill. Are you listening?
你想把余下的任期都消耗在
Do you want to spend the rest of your presidency
维护你死去的丈夫
defending your dead husband,
和他的
defending his...
行为上吗
deeds?
因为他们会确保
Because they will make sure
你在白宫不论清醒还是沉睡的
that every waking and even sleeping moment
每一时每一刻都无法摆脱他
of your time in the White House is about him!
为过去一百天里的事做弥补
Make amends for the last hundred days.
你就能拥有接下来的四年
Then you can have the next four years.
你周末
When you present the
去志远俱乐部颁奖学金时
scholarship at the Take Aim Club this weekend,
安奈特·谢泼德也会到场
Annette Shepherd will be there.
她是董事会成员  他们都捐款
She's on the board. They're all donors.
跟你的老朋友一起出席
Appear with your old friend...
把法案签了
and sign this bill.
我可以帮你的
You know, I can help you...
在谢泼德兄妹那里  我会跟他们打交道
with the Shepherds. I know how to talk to them.
请跟我解释一下  你为什么觉得
And please, please explain to me why you thought...
昨天提拔那个
putting that elevated intern
实习生去接待媒体对你有好处
in front of the press yesterday serves you.
-因为她诚实  -我准备了米奇·格雷泽
- Because she's honest. - I had Mitch Glazer lined up.
-他有30年的...  -因为她不是米奇
- He's got 30 years of-- - Because she's not Mitch.
因为我知道你赶走了肖恩
Because I know you pushed out Sean.
肖恩·杰弗瑞斯不愿说实话
Sean Jeffries had a hard time telling the truth.
你的那版实话吗
Your truth?
是的  维系你权力的版本
Yes, the one that keeps you in power.
现在怎么
And now what?
你拿她的天真换他的野心吗
We've traded his ambition for her naïveté?
我相信她
I believe her.
别人也会的
And so will everyone else.
-抱歉  你需要我...  -不
- I'm sorry, do you need me to-- - No, no,
我其实是来找你的
actually, I was looking for you.
我想为昨天的事道歉
I wanted to apologize for yesterday.
不  没事的
No, please.
-我很高兴你能帮忙  -好吧
- I was happy to have your help. - Okay.
你知道肖恩不会回来了吧
You know Sean's not coming back, right?
我听说了
I heard.
总统肯定是看中了你的哪一点
The president must see something in you.
你觉得是什么
What do you think that is?
这是个很棒的机会
It was an amazing opportunity.
我听说这个位置
And I've heard there are
有一些很不错的候选人
some wonderful candidates for the position.
是啊
Yeah.
在确定之前
Well, until then...
你继续
why don't you to continue on
做代理新闻发言人吧
as acting press secretary.
当然  好  先生
Of course. Yes, sir.
谢谢你和总统
And thank you and the president.
你相信她吗  斯图尔特小姐
Do you believe in her, Miss Stewart?
我相信
I do.
我问是因为
I ask because...
要知道有一些厉害的势力
I want you to know there are powerful forces out there
很想看她失败
that are invested in seeing her fail.
所以你会听到谣传  和暗示
So you're gonna hear rumors. You're gonna hear innuendos.
你得照你的要点讲
You'll need to stick to your talking points.
别被些不怀好意的问题带沟里去
Not get lured off-track with, what, salacious questions.
我明白
I understand.
现在  我算是幕僚长
Right now, I'm the de facto chief of staff.
所以  如果你需要
So, if you need...
帮助或建议
help or advice,
你知道去哪找我
you know where to find me.
祝你好运
Good luck.
谢谢
Thank you.
洛杉矶外的圣费尔南多谷起火了
There's a fire burning in the Valley outside of Los Angeles.
所以基金会就派志愿者过去
So, the Foundation sends volunteers in,
让他们加入应用
we sign them up for the app.
在贝尔波特加入的人有多少
How many signed up in Bellport?
区域内外大概有五万部手机
In and around the area, close to 50,000 phones.
除了大火  还有狭长地带的洪水
But beside the fires, there's flooding in the Panhandle.
大雨已持续数日
It's been raining for days.
北达科他州一条管线爆裂
There's a pipeline that's burst in North Dakota.
这是我外甥想的
And my nephew came up with this?
是基于已有技术  但是
Well, it's based on pre-existing technology, but...
他看到了潜力
he saw the potential.
基本上  他们交出了自己的手机
Essentially they're handing over their phones,
你也知道
which as you know,
那个现在基本上就是他们自身的一部分了
is basically an extension of the self at this point.
邓肯称之为"我们灵魂的石棺"
Duncan calls them "the sarcophagi of our souls."
我们能采集手机信息
We'll be crawling peoples' phones.
你可以决定大家什么时候看到什么
You get to decide what people see and when.
弗兰克是因为这风景才选这里住的吗
Did Frank take this room because of the view?
好像是吧
Yes, I think he did.
你尊敬他
You respected him.
你怕他吗
Did you fear him?
是的
Yes.
但你总能知道你和他的立场
But you always knew where you stood with him.
她呢
And her?
永远不知道
You never know.
工厂的工人用应用了吗
Did the workers at the plant sign up for the app?
-大都用了  -很好
- Most of them did, yes. - Good.
很好
Good.
我很高兴你来为我们工作  赛斯
I'm glad you're working with us, Seth.
你对安德伍德夫妇的了解
Your perspective, when it comes to the Underwoods,
还有我外甥
my nephew.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
退休探员吗
Retired agents?
他们现在是自由职业了
They're freelance now.
为奈克西斯安保工作  很多人都这样
Working for Nexis Securities. A lot of guys do it.
据说他俩这一周来都在
Apparently these two have been on the ground in Gaffney
加夫尼
for the last week or so.
-谁雇佣的  -我们还不知道
- Hired by who? - We don't know yet.
但他们挣的钱够多  其中一人刚在
But they're making enough so that one of them just purchased
切萨皮克湾买了第二栋房子
a second home on the Chesapeake Bay.
他们
They...
闯进了您在加夫尼的住所  女士
broke into your Gaffney residence, ma'am.
什么  特勤局呢
What? Where was Secret Service?
我怎么没收到通知
And why wasn't I alerted?
因为没人收到通知
Because no one was alerted.
他们什么都没动
They left it completely untouched,
至少看上去是的
as far as anyone can tell.
那你怎么知道有人去过
How did you know anyone was there, then?
一个失眠的邻居
An insomniac neighbor
看到屋里有手机屏幕的亮光
who spotted the light from a phone screen inside.
拍照吧
Taking pictures, I'm assuming.
天呐
My, my, my.
加夫尼的夜生活丰富起来了
Night life in Gaffney certainly has picked up.
从我小时候开始的
Started when I was a kid.
只要有机会
Whenever the opportunity would present itself,
我就会伸手到衣兜里去  看能找到什么
I'd slip my hand into a coat pocket to see what I could find.
陌生人的衣兜是窥视其灵魂的窗口
A stranger's pocket is a window into his soul.
你发现了什么
And what did you find?
安全套
Condoms.
薄荷糖  钥匙
Mints. Keys.
你把你发现的东西偷走了吗
Did you steal what you found?
没偷薄荷糖  那太残忍了
Not the mints. Because that would be cruel.
是你吗
Was that you...
去机场路上那事
on the way to the airport?
是想教训她吗
Were you trying to teach her a lesson?
-去找比尔吧  -拜托
- Talk to Bill. - Come on.
我已经跟他谈过了
I already did.
-她迟到了  -她是总统嘛
- She's late. - Yeah, she's the president.
你就是对强势女人心软
You know, you have a weakness for strong women.
真的
No, really.
你觉得她们需要你帮助
You think they need your help.
不是吧
Really?
-还抽呢  -不
- Still? - No, no.
我现在嚼口香糖了
I chew now.
我就是喜欢
I just like to...
玩这个
play with this.
等等
Wait.
她来了
She's here.
总统女士  邓肯·谢泼德
Madam President, Duncan Shepherd.
-你好  -克莱尔
- Hello. - Claire.
安奈特
Annette.
你见过邓肯了
I see you've met Duncan.
-我们走吧  -好
- Shall we? - Yes.
可不许再抽我手了
Don't ever recoil from me again.
50多棒啊
Ain't 50 nifty?
你上次把我拉进洗手间里
I think the last time you dragged me into a bathroom,
好像是为了炫耀你的吻痕
it was to show off your hickey.
我觉得你哥哥不会收手的  安奈特
I don't think your brother is gonna let up, Annette.
除非我直接俯首称臣
Until he gets his ring kissed directly, I think.
这让我想起了你曾经的丈夫
Reminds me of someone you were married to.
不  比尔和弗兰西斯可很不一样
No. Bill and Francis are very different people.
是啊
Agreed.
我睡过他一次
You know I slept with him once.
你哥哥吗
Your brother?
你丈夫
Your husband.
我知道
I know.
有意思
Interesting.
不过想来  也不奇怪
Though, come to think of it, I guess it makes sense.
什么
What does?
你们的婚姻不介意那些
That your marriage allowed for that.
那是98年的竞选
Well, it was the '98 campaign.
弗兰西斯的对手势头很猛
Francis was facing a robust challenger,
你们在华府的哪个筹款宴会上碰面了
and there you were at some DC fundraiser or other.
是在联合车站
It was at the Union Station,
-东大堂  -对
- East Hall. - Yes.
你晃着手里的支票簿
And there you were, dangling your checkbook.
所以听上去像是挺不错的交易
So, it sounds like a favorable transaction all around.
-他是那么跟你说的吗  -我从不问细节
- Is that what he told you? - I never asked for details.
我当时是挺好奇
I mean, I was curious.
真的
I really was.
他吻技还不错
He was a good kisser, I'll say that.
但其他的  太不给力了
But then the rest was so underwhelming.
感觉他的心没全在那儿
Felt like he wasn't all there.
就好像他没...
Like, he wasn't...
完全投入
all in, so to speak.
当然了  我第一个念头...
Of course, my first thought, and...
大部分女人都会如此吧
isn't this true of most women?
我想会不会是我
Was to wonder if it was me.
我的床技是不是
Was I somehow less skilled
比我自以为的要差
than I like to believe I am?
这我就不知道了  安奈特
Well, I can't really answer to that, Annette.
我知道
I can.
是他
It was him.
而且
And...
我敢说他跟你也一向是如此
I bet it was never very different with you.
哪怕是你
Even you.
金发女神
The blonde goddess.
哪怕是跟你  对吗
Even with you. Am I right?
我真的现在才意识到
It's really only dawning on me now.
你做出的牺牲
The sacrifice you made.
我都有点可怜你
I sort of pity you.
你这么多年来是怎样有苦说不出
What you must have denied yourself all those years.
我现在就要让你闭嘴了  安奈特
And this is where I tell you to shut your mouth, Annette.
你根本不懂婚姻
You don't know anything about marriage,
跟别说我的了
much less mine.
随便你怎么安慰自己  克莱尔
Tell yourself whatever you want, Claire.
我们都清楚真相
We both know the truth.
他在走廊那边的备餐厨房等你
He's waiting for you down the hall in the prep kitchen.
我哥哥
My brother.
我现在还会呢
I can still do it by the way.
你呢
Can you?
你错过了晚餐
Well, you missed dinner.
你想吃什么  我可以让他们给你做
I can have 'em make you whatever you like.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
秘诀在于放多少
The secret here is how much
柠檬汁
lemon juice you put in.
能调和黄油
Balance out the butter.
大家都喜欢荷兰汁
People and hollandaise.
觉得那是钱的味道
They think it tastes like money.
-酒店般的享受  -你想找什么
- A night at the hotel. - What where you looking for?
加夫尼宅邸里没有什么值钱的东西
There's nothing in the Gaffney home of value.
弗兰克做过些事
Frank did things.
你怎么
And you just, what?
就当没看见吗
Look the other way?
你冲我开的那一枪  这么鲁莽不像你啊
That shot you took at me, it's not like you to be so reckless.
你不好吓
You don't scare easy.
这事关国家的未来
The future of our country is at stake.
这听上去
Does that sound...
做作吗  天真吗
pat to you, naive?
完全不会
No, not at all.
你以为我在五角大楼就没朋友了吗  克莱尔
Do you think I don't have friends at the Pentagon, Claire?
你或许想让我的四年任期很不好过...
You may want to make my four years in office miserable--
我只是希望你按说好的做
All I want you to do is behave, as promised.
你可以去挖戒指  或其他你能挖到的东西
You can dig up a ring or whatever else you can get your hands on.
但那不代表
But that doesn't mean
我不会也让你一样不好过
I won't make your time a living hell as well.
雷蒙德·塔斯克有次说你
Raymond Tusk said about you one time,
我们是一起出席什么晚宴  他说...
some dinner we were at, he just said it--
我现在是应该
This is where I'm supposed to be
有点害怕听到他说了什么
a little bit afraid of the answer,
-是吧  -他说"我不知道
- I suppose. - He said, "I don't know,
她真是个人
whether or not she's a person...
还是在扮演一个人"
or just playing the part of one."
我当时还觉得这话很奇怪  但或许这是真的
And I thought it was so strange at the time, but maybe it's true.
你真是
Just...
不通人情
unreachable.
我知道这对你很难
I know it'll be hard for you.
但你得平等地对待我  比尔
But you're going to have to treat me as an equal, Bill.
你怎么处理你丈夫的遗嘱的
What did you do with your husband's will?
那是份可撤销的信托
It was a revocable trust.
我都处理好了
All done.
我不是说那个
I'm not talking about that one.
我是说另一个
I'm talking about the other one.
新的那份
The new one.
道格·斯坦普肯定会想看到那份
Bet Doug Stamper would love to see the contents of that one.
上面写了什么
What's in there anyway?
你竟不惜一切
That you would go to such lengths
让他看不到
to keep him from it?
克莱尔·黑尔有个秘密
Claire Hale has a secret.
道格拉斯·斯坦普这会儿正在跟联邦检察官
Douglas Stamper is meeting with the US District Attorney
会面
as we speak.
他出来了  克莱尔
He's out, Claire.
他不会再回去了
And he's not going back in.
你需要我的帮助
Now, you need my help.
今晚晚些时候
Later tonight,
我要眼看着你签署
I'm going to watch you sign that bill
你桌上的那份法案
that's sitting on your desk.
"对于死者
"To the dead,
王国毫无意义
a kingdom means nothing.
他们已经拥有安宁和永恒了"
They have their requiem and eternity."
是歌剧《麦克白》  不是戏剧
That's Macbeth. The opera, not the play.
你现在只需要出去
All you have to do now is just go on out there
跟你最久最亲爱的朋友站在一起
with your oldest, dearest friend and...
把她的手高高地举起来
hold her hand up high.
总统女士
Madam President.
你并不真认为美军是无关紧要的吧[S03E02]
You don't really think the military is irrelevant?
我在我的法官室里
I watched your confirmation
观看了你的联合国大使提名表决
from my chambers for the UN.
不是我最好的时刻
Wasn't my finest hour.
笑得最响的[男]人...
Well, he who laughs loudest--
还是"笑到最后"
Or is it "laughs last"?
"最后"  是"女人"
"Last." "She."
-我是文森特·阿布佐  -第九巡回法院
- Vincent Abruzzo. - Ninth Circuit.
我很不适应这样的场合
I am no good at functions like this.
我一般都在这样的活动上找把椅子
I tend to find a chair at these things
然后就坐一晚上
and sit in it for the rest of the evening.
-总统女士  -嗯  很荣幸认识你
- Madam President. - Yes. Well, it's been a pleasure.
总统女士  容我说一句
Madam President, if I may say,
我很高兴总统办公室总算迎来一位女性
I'm so glad that we finally have a woman in the Oval Office.
虽然历时很久  但...
The arc of history is long, but--
中年白人男子的统治结束了
The reign of the middle-aged white man is over.
比尔·谢泼德这样不肯放手的人  必须下台
The Bill Shepherds of the world who won't let go, have to go.
除了你  还有别人知道寄给他的那份文件吗
Does anyone except you know about the document that came for him?
当然没有
No, of course not.
因为如果有别人拿到了那份遗嘱
Because if anyone else gets their hand on that will--
那完全是你知我知
That is strictly between us.
我们才刚发现他失踪了
We only just discovered that he was missing.
我联系了联邦检察官  才得知
I put a call into the US Attorney and was just informed
指控已撤销
charges have been dropped.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible?
我几天前以为自己丢了手机
I thought I'd lost my phone a couple of days ago, but...
但现在我可以确定
But now I'm certain that
是他拿走了  打电话做了笔交易
he took it and reached out to make a deal.
我可以选好大陪审团
I can have a grand jury impaneled
一周内就开始对证人进行取证
and we can be taking testimony from witnesses within a week.
你找了谁
Who do you have?
杜兰特国务卿吗
Secretary Durant?
还有别人
And others.
我相信不用我告诉你是非对错
I'm sure I don't need to talk to you about what's right or wrong.
但依我的经验  大部分人到最后
But in my experience, most people, in the end,
都会不惜一切地保护自己
will do whatever they need to, to save themselves.
你觉得你的胜算大吗
Do you think you have a strong enough case?
那要看你的了
That depends on you.
如果我要拿自己冒险
If I'm gonna put myself on the line,
我需要知道你能赢
I need to know you're going to win.
这个城市可以很记仇
This can be a very unforgiving town.
我在给你重新开始的机会
I'm giving you a chance to start over.
-得了  -我可以拿豁免权
- Come on. - I can offer you immunity
换取你的证词
for your testimony.
但是  当然了  斯坦普先生  我并不能就
But, Mr. Stamper, of course, I can't give you any guarantees
你或前总统的名声做出担保
when it comes to your reputation or that of the former president.
你得在公开法庭上作证
You would have to testify in an open court.
这是我们的条件
That is the deal.
我要咨询下我的律师
I should consult with my lawyers.
谢谢你前来  斯坦普先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Stamper.
与我们一起支持达拉斯年轻女性
Join us in supporting the Dallas Scholarship Fund
奖学金基金
for Young Women:
志远
Take aim.
看看这些了不起的面孔
Look at these marvelous faces.
她们是未来的面孔
The faces of our future.
我非常荣幸
And I am so, so honored
能够向大家介绍
to be chosen to introduce to you
美国总统  克莱尔·安德伍德
the President of the United States, Claire Underwood.
我看着这些杰出的年轻姑娘
I look at these brilliant young women
激动得难以言表
and words fail me.
这是什么
What's this?
他们发给了我们这个  它们能干什么
They gave us these. What are they gonna do?
我可不喝那水
Yeah, I'm not drinking the water,
绝不  我告诉你
no fucking way, I'll tell you that.
实在不行我就去坎顿买
I'll go all the way to Canton to buy it, if I have to.
格雷森先生
And... Mr. Grayson,
关于这个应用  他还对你说了什么
what else did he tell you about the app?
没说什么了  你可以上网去看
Nothing. You can go online and check it out.
因为我认识的很多人
'Cause a lot of people I know
在总统走后还是下载了
signed up for it even after the president left.
他说...
He said...
格雷森先生吗
Mr. Grayson?
对  他
Yeah, him.
它们能让我们在事发前就知道
That they were gonna tell us what was gonna happen
-要发生什么  -那怎么说
- before it happens. - How?
我不知道
Look, I don't know.
伊萨卡在哪里
Ithaca's, like, where?
希腊有一个
There's one in Greece.
纽约州北也有一个
And the other's in upstate New York.
猜猜哪个是我的家乡
Guess which one I'm from.
是一份报纸  每周印发一期
It's a paper, it comes out once a week.
这是不可避免的
It was going to happen,
因为之前就发生过
because it happened before.
我们都上报到环保署了  但是
We complained all the way to the EPA, but...
没办法
whatever.
只不过这次的爆炸比较严重
Only this time the explosion was bad.
是啊  死了人  公司早就知道
And yeah, some guys died. And the company knew.
他们知道的
They knew.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
真巧  我刚煮上咖啡
Good timing. I just put on coffee.
现在喝咖啡有点晚了吧
A little late for coffee.
我们有好多要谈呢
Well, we have so much to talk about.
我很高兴你出来了  道格
I'm glad you're out, Doug.
我都不知道你为什么会进去
I don't know what you were doing in there.
联邦检察官怎么样了
How's the US Attorney?
杜兰特国务卿在商谈她的出庭
Secretary Durant's negotiating her appearance.
如果
And if...
凯茜被劝说不去了呢
Cathy should somehow be dissuaded?
-不发声了呢  -那一切都不了了之
- Silenced? - Then it all goes away.
是啊  但他们还是会想知道
Yes, but they'll still want to know
谁知道什么  什么时候
who knew what, when.
我挺清楚的
I feel pretty clear.
你觉得是我叫你背锅的
You think it was me who asked you to take the fall
-因为是我开的口  -他告诉我是你了
- just because I said the words, right? - He told me it was you.
-他悄悄对我说的  -你就信了
- He whispered it in my ear. - And you believed him.
你总是相信他
Like you always believed him.
我是这么想的  佐伊·巴恩斯自杀了
Well, here's what I believe. Zoe Barnes killed herself--
其他的事我会得到赦免
And I expected to be pardoned for the rest.
他死后  我一直受到束缚
Since his death, my hands have been tied.
但我认为上天给了我们一份礼物
But I believe the universe has given us a gift.
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
这么说吧
Well...
我们都失去了一个
We both lost someone
改变了我们人生轨迹的人
who shaped the course of our lives.
有好的改变  也有坏的
For good, but also for ill.
现在我们
And now here we are
意外地自由了
unexpectedly free.
可以选择不一样的方法
To take a different tack.
我们想做什么都行  道格
We can do whatever we want, Doug.
我们的命运一直纠缠在一起
And we've been entwined, you and I,
不管愿不愿意
like it or not,
这几十年来都是如此
for decades now.
但我觉得
But I think...
我们有权分道扬镳了
we deserve to go our separate ways.
唯一的问题是
The only problem is
我们有个紧急的问题要处理
we have something urgent to attend to
凯茜·杜兰特
called Cathy Durant.
然后我们就终于自由了
And then we can finally be free.
做我们真正想做的
Do what we really want.
做我们需要做的
Do what we need to do.
道格·斯坦普想要什么
What does Doug Stamper want?
你是想抹去他吗
Are you trying to erase him?
因为你做不到
Because you can't.
我没有别的意思
I'm not trying to do anything
只是想做好现任美国总统
except be the sitting President of the United States.
你不该认定
It's wrong to assume
弗兰西斯的野心跟我的完全一致  道格
Francis's ambitions directly aligned with mine, Doug.
要想不被与他的可疑行为联系在一起
The best way to not to be associated with his questionable deeds
就得做好事
is to do good.
至少我是打算这么做的
That's what I plan to do, anyway.
你觉得好笑  是吗
Oh, you find that funny, do you?
是真的
Well, it's true.
我就不懂他看好了你什么
I never understood what he saw in you.
这副皮囊的确不错
I mean the outside, sure.
但内心
But the inside...
-莉安的死  -不
- LeAnn's death. - No.
你根本没在乎过她
You never cared for her.
并不非得如此
It wasn't necessary.
我也这么跟他说了
And I told him so.
但是...
And yet...
道格  帮个忙
Doug, do me a favor.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
拜托
Please.
他把这个留给了你
He wanted you to have them.
这种事就你这个年纪来说
For this to happen at this point in your life,
预后并不乐观
the prognosis is not good.
我知道
I know.
有人杀了弗兰西斯
Somebody killed Francis,
却不希望他死
and yet they don't want him to die.
我们最后一次通话的那晚
That last night, the last time we spoke,
就是我在总统办公室里拒接了他的电话
was when I declined his phone call in the Oval Office.
已经快两个月了  他不想再等了
It had been close to two months, and he was tired of waiting.
于是他自己跑来了白宫
So he showed up here in the White House.
像个小贼
Like a thief.
当时好可怕
It was terrifying.
他暴跳如雷  说话都不清楚了
He was furious, slurring his words.
"你怎么就不能乖乖听话  克莱尔"
"Why can't you do as you're told, Claire?"
我告诉世人他死在了我们的床上
I told the world that he died in our bed,
但那不是事实
but that's not the truth.
我那晚上把自己锁在了我的房间里
I locked myself in my room that night,
早上醒来时  发现他死在了自己房里
woke up in the morning and found him dead in his.
他们杀了他  好让我闭嘴
They killed him to shut me up.
我必须彻底埋葬弗兰西斯
I need to bury Francis, once and for all.
签字还需要人帮忙吗
Do you need help signing it?
别  比尔  谢泼德  够了
No. Bill. Shepherd, enough.
其实  我有个条件
I actually have one condition.
放回去
Put it back.
根据美国劳工部发布的10月就业数据
新增非农就业岗位25万  失业率3.7%
工资增长速度为2008年以来最快
许多特朗普的支持者认为  这些数字
一要归功于共和党2017年末通过的减税法案
二要归功于特朗普政府一系列的去监管措施
在过去两年中  特朗普政府信守共和党"小政府""少插手"的理念
大幅度废除联邦行政法规和监管条例
到今年7月为止  白宫共废除176项监管性法规  节省开支230亿美元
其中环保署在2018年就取消/废除了10项法规
而这一数字预计会在2019年增长到30项
但去监管在刺激经济增长的同时  也增加了发生环保灾难的可能
今年三月  美国英国多家媒体揭露  在2016年大选期间
一家名为"剑桥分析"的公司在用户不知情的情况下
从脸书上获取用户个人信息  并将其卖给特朗普竞选团队
新闻曝光后  脸书股价大幅下滑  执行总裁扎克伯格
也不得不到国会山作证  接受议员们的严词问询
此后脸书和其它一些网站在用户隐私政策上进行了改进
过去十年中  互联网和移动终端在美国政治生活中发挥的作用越来越大
但同时也带来了一系列的严重问题
目前美国共和党和民主党都对社交网络公司的一些操作有很大意见
不过双方所关注的问题不尽相同
民主党指责社交网络上假新闻泛滥  影响了选举结果
而共和党则抱怨硅谷的公司在网络上刻意打压保守派言论
因此要求立法监管社交网络的呼声越来越大
硅谷数家大公司的老板都曾被叫到国会山接受议员们的问询
支持和反对监管的两种力量也正在激烈较量中  尚未分出胜负
美国有着非常严格的环保法规  联邦环保署权力很大
下属的环保执法机构犯罪调查处虽然只有200名左右的探员
但是这些环保先锋有非常独立的执法权  可以携带枪支  执行逮捕
2017年联邦环保署的执法队伍共罚没收缴了50亿美元的款项
在罪案调查过程中  环保署的执法部门也会同其它联邦执法部门合作
不过剧中被调驻到国防部的情况在现实生活中还不曾出现
环保署自身执法权限很大  在对付大公司的时候一般也不需要五角大楼介入
近年来倒在环保署铁拳下的最大一个目标是德国的大众公司
由于在尾气排放问题上作假  在环保署的调查下
大众公司被罚款28亿美元  并支付15亿美元的补偿款
涉案的一名公司高管和一名工程师也被判入狱
因为共和党的去监管主张  在特朗普主政之后  环保署力量被大幅削弱
其下属的执法部门调查的案件也照往年有很大幅度的减少